martjack.com 2018-05-15

# The Privacy Policy Of MartJack.com

MartJack uses your information on an aggregated basis to do such things as operate our web sites and enhance our web sites. We statistically analyze site usage, including the behavior of our Members, to improve the content, layout, and services of the MartJack web sites, as well as to enhance our marketing and promotional efforts.

We share aggregate information about our Members with third parties, such as advertisers or partners, for marketing and promotional purposes, to provide your with discounted prices of their products and services. However, except as otherwise contemplated in this Privacy Policy, we do not disclose any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission or as otherwise required by law.

We use the information we collect to better understand your needs. Additionally for the MartJack subscription Services we use the information we collect to process payments, confirm renewal charges or payments to your account, administer your account and the like.

Finally, we may use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important functionality changes to the web site, new Services, and special offers.

MartJack uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. We make every effort to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. In addition, we always use a secure connection when collecting personal financial information from you. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

Your MartJack account is password-protected so in addition to those partners or agents who may provide you services, only you and those you designate can access it and view the member information relevant to your account. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. Remember to log out of your account and close your browser window when you are done. This ensures that others cannot access your personal information if your computer is accessible to others.

This policy is periodically reviewed by MartJack and is subject to changes made by MartJack. Therefore, please check this Privacy Policy periodically and you may refer to the date posted at the top of this page to determine when this policy was last updated. Use of the MartJack software/ Service(s) constitutes your absolute consent to our privacy policy then in effect.

MartJack uses the AdWords and Remarketing Lists features of Google Analytics for Display Advertisers. 

MartJack and Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to [www.martjack.com](http://www.martjack.com/) web sites. This means that vendors including Google will display [www.martjack.com](http://www.martjack.com/) promotional material on other sites you visit across the Internet.

You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertisers including AdWords and opt-out of customized Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Preferences Manager. 

To provide web site visitors more choice on how their data is collected by Google Analytics, Google has developed an Opt-out Browser add-on, which is available by visiting Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on, to enable you to opt-out of Google’s programs.
